performancing.com 2007-06-24

# Privacy Policy | Performancing.com

**Submitted byNick Wilson on November 12, 2005 - 12:21pm in **

Thank you for visiting Performancing. This policy explains how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this policy.

This policy may be changed at any time. Any changes will be posted. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy each and every time you visit the site.

## Cookies

This Web site uses cookies to help us collect information about users. These can be disabled in major web browsers. Please see your browser's documentation or help options for more information on how to disable cookies.

## Information Collection

We collect certain information about users who visit this site, including user actions and click paths, domain name/IP addresses and browser types, as well as other information. We use this information mainly to track referrals and analyze user behavior. We also collect personal information, including email addresses, from registered users.

## Distribution of Information

We may share information with government agencies or other companies helping us to investigate or prevent fraud. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required to do so by law; or, (2) preventing or attempting to prevent actual or potential unauthorized actions or fraud; or, (3) investigating past fraud. We will not however share user information, including email addresses, with third parties for marketing purposes.

## Privacy Policies of Web Sites Hyperlinked to from Performancing

We are not responsible for the policies of Web sites that we hyperlink to. If you visit other Web sites hyperlinked from this site, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
